We are currently on a sheet.
当前我们打开了一个工作表
Sheets are where we can build visualizations.
“工作表”(Sheet)是可以创建可视化图表的地方
Let's go over some of the various areas on the screen.
我们来看看屏幕上的一些不同区域
At the top, we have the menus.
顶部是菜单
The menus contain a lot of powerful options and I
菜单包含很多强大的选项
recommend clicking through to see what options they have.
我建议你点击看看它们都是些什么选项
The logo button, here,
这里的标志按钮
brings us back to the start experience where we can access
可以让我们回到开始页面
saved data sources recently opened or pinned workbooks.
以便访问最近打开或锁定的工作簿中保存的数据源
To the left of the screen is the data pane.
屏幕左侧是数据窗格
If we're on the data tab,
如果我们位于数据选项卡上
the top lists all open data sources.
顶部会列出所有打开的数据源
And, depending on which one is selected,
而且 根据你选中的数据源
the fields from that data source are listed below
下面会列出该数据源的字段(Fields)
broken out into dimensions and measures.
并将这些字段分解成“维度”(Dimensions)和“度量”(Measures)
The data pane will also show any sets or parameters we have.
数据窗格还将显示我们拥有的任何集合或参数
If we open the maps layer or the format pane,
如果我们打开地图图层或格式窗格
these temporarily cover the data pane.
它们会暂时覆盖数据窗格
If you click on the analytics tab,
点击“分析”(Analytics) 选项卡
we can bring out pieces of our analysis directly as drag and drop elements.
会显示可直接作为拖放元素的分析部分
If they're not relevant to the type of view,
如果它们与视图类型无关
certain elements will be grayed out such as totals on a timeline.
某些元素将变灰 例如时间轴上的“总计”(Totals)
If we select something like a trend line,
如果我们选择“趋势线”(Trend Line)
we can bring it to any of these dropdown areas to control aspects of its properties,
则可以进一步选取下拉区域中的任意项 以控制其属性的各个方面
like model type or which measure it should be applied to.
如模型类型或应用于哪个度量
New sheets are found down here at the bottom.
新建工作表位于底部的这个位置
We can create sheets,
我们可以使用这些选项卡
dashboards, or stories with these tabs.
创建工作表、“仪表板”(Dashboard)或“故事”(Stroy)
We can do things like rename sheets,
我们可以重命名工作表、复制工作表、复制格式
duplicate sheets, copy formatting, many other things.
还可以做其他很多事情
Finally, and perhaps more importantly, we have the shelves.
最后 也许更重要的是 我们可以使用“功能区”(Shelves)
Use can be built by dragging and dropping fields from
可以通过将数据窗格中的字段直接拖放到画布中
the data pane into the canvas directly or onto the shelves.
或拖放到功能区中来进行
The shelves are sometimes referred to as cards.
功能区有时被称为“卡”(Cards)
There's the column shelf and the row shelf up here,
这里是“列”(Column)功能区和“行”(Row)功能区
the pages and filter shelves, and the marks cards.
“页面”(Pages)功能区、“筛选器”(Filters)功能区和“标记”(Marks)卡
The marks card is made up of several other shells.
标记卡又由几个“框”(Shells)组成
Each of which can have fields placed on
每个框上面都可以放置字段
them and can be clicked on to edit their characteristics.
通过点击还能编辑框的特性
Change in the marks type can change the shelves
更改标记类型可以更改标记卡上的功能区
on the marks cards such as selecting shape brings up the shape shelf.
例如选择 Shape 类型会建立 Shape 功能区
Depending on the composition of the view,
根据视图的构成情况
there can be multiple marks cards, one for each measure.
可以有多个标记卡 每个度量一个
Legends such as color, size,
当将字段放置在颜色、大小或形状功能区上时
and shape will automatically be created when a field is placed on the color,
Tableau 会自动创建
size, or shape shelf.
诸如颜色、大小和形状等图例
However, legends can be removed by clicking on the menu and selecting hide card.
不过 通过点击菜单并选择隐藏卡可以删除图例
To bring the legend back,
若要恢复显示图例
right click anywhere off the canvas itself,
右击画布上的任意位置
select legend and choose the one you want.
选择“图例”(Legends) 然后选择你要的那一个